Please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Let's practice.
We will throw 10 balls each.
I have never thrown a ball with both
hands.
So, I will try with both hands.
It's fun.
Ready?
What is it?
Wait, it's Karin.
It's strong.
I did it.
It's fun.
It's a bowling battle.
Yeah!
It's a perfect match for an event.
Let's go!
I'm going to go to Sakai!
I'm going to go to Yoshikawa!
See!
Wow!
I'm a woman who does what I have to do!
It's so good. It's cute.
It's the first time to eat and drink
purple sweet potato.
It's not sweet.
It's good.
Cheers!
Thank you for watching.
I want to eat Tonkotsu Ramen.
I can see your sunglasses.
I'm embarrassed if I can't see your
sunglasses.
I'm going to eat a lot of cheese.
I've been to Shimokitazawa once.
At that time, Julia said she wanted to
eat cheese dog.
I want to eat something.
Do you eat potato?
This is a potato pancake.
Wow.
Look at this.
I've never seen this before.
How can I eat this?
OK, let's monitor.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm here.
Is it going to end soon?
Japanese Idol.
Are you looking forward to it?
Yeah!
It's cool that the members can speak
English.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been to a lot of Olympics.
Okay, what's your hobby?
Swimming
Oh, swimming?
Do you swim in the music video?
No?
No
Okay, that's cool
Yay!
You can't
English speak
Speak English?
No
Really?
Sleeping
What did you say?
What was it?
Sleeping
Oh, you mean how are you doing?
What did you say?
I don't know
I thought you were asking how long I've
been swimming
I've been watching you
I couldn't see you at all
I really wanted to do this
I always do this
I'm sorry
What?
I was surprised
I was surprised too
What's wrong?
I thought you were asking how long I've
been swimming
I was surprised too
blank stare
Oh my gosh!
It was a very brave performance!
Today is the special collaboration
between Takemiki Sendai and Anrakutei.
Let me take an insert.
This is a collaboration video of
Takemiki Sendai and Anrakutei.
This is it.
I'm not sure if I'm in the frame.
Are you OK?
First, Julia.
Julia?
Where are you from?
I'm not in the frame.
Here she is.
And...
Kanamin.
I'm not in the frame.
I'm in the frame.
Bambi.
And... Julia.
Wait.
I was in the frame.
I'm in the frame.
She is cute.
And...
She is a meat.
Koizumi is kind.
I like her.
I like you more.
Ready, go!
You like meat more than spring?
Well, yes.
Why? Why do you like meat more than
spring?
Why?
What should I do?
I like you.
I like you, too.
I don't know.
You don't say.
OK. I'll eat meat.
I like you, too.
It wasgarile.
If you want to be lifted, do it with
you or with a friend.
Téé!
Yes, the second part of the birthday
party will start soon.
I'm nervous.
But when this second part is over, the
birthday party will be over.
I'll do my best.
I'll enjoy it.
Today is Hiori's birthday.
Yeah!
Hiorin!
My Hiorin!
Look at this.
This is Hiori's birthday goods.
It's so cute.
Look at this.
It has a spider.
It's so cute.
Did you get it?
I got it, too.
I don't want to use it, so I want to
decorate it on the wall.
It's cute.
Did you enjoy the performance of Piyo?
I was invited as a special guest.
I didn't expect to be invited.
I'm so happy.
I don't know if I could support you
well, but I hope you enjoyed it.
I had a lot of fun.
I was laughing a lot when I saw Piyo's
performance in the rehearsal.
It was fun.
I'm sure you're laughing, too.
At Piyo's concert.
That's all.
Happy 18th birthday, Tio!
Happy birthday, Tio!
Thank you for your hard work!
I'm the best! I'm the best!
It's over!
Everyone, please come to the Hirano
Saitama Festival!
Thank you very much!
You're the best!
Wow!
You said I'm the best!
It's amazing.
In the first part, I was nervous.
I was nervous, but in the second part,
I was able to relax.
I think I was able to relax.
I think I was able to show all my
strength.
I feel like I've calmed down.
I feel like I'm turning 18.
I want to show everyone my strength.
I can feel that everyone loves me and
supports me.
I'm really grateful to the promoters.
Thank you for your support.
Everyone is supporting me.
I will do my best to support everyone.
I would be happy if you could support
Toki and Yoshikawa.
Thank you very much for today.
You're the best.
Not Kanami.
You?
I'm the best?
Thank you for watching!
I drank too much because of you.
Thank you for your concern.
Thank you.
I didn't expect to be a guest of this
show.
We sang a love game of a man and a
woman.
I wanted to make it an interesting
show.
So, I did as I thought.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'm glad I was able to support Tio.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
I'm so full.
I'm going to sleep now.
I can't.
I thought you said yes.
You are a citizen again.
Really?
What about Juri?
I'm not a citizen.
I'm a citizen.
What?
Juri.
Good morning.
Oh!
It's over.
I thought it was a human.
It's a citizen.
I didn't know.
Human?
Citizen.
Citizen?
No, it's a citizen.
It's a human, isn't it?
No, it's not a human.
Now...
I can't lie.
So...
I'm sorry.
Truth?
You're saying the truth now, right?
Truth...
I'm looking at you like this.
Truth.
I'm doing a lot of things now.
Wait, wait.
You really have to form a team.
Werewolf?
Not werewolf.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching!
Hello!
Come on, show yourself!
Look at this! It's huge!
The accessories are so big that you
can't see my face.
I think you stood out on stage.
Yeah, because you're shining.
Your outfit is so shiny.
Thank you for watching!
Show me the blueberry.
No.
Why?
Here is a quarter of melon.
Lemon.
You said cup.
Bye!
The first day is over.
Is it over?
Oh, right. It was our first TIFU.
How was it?
It was fun. It was quick.
We had four songs today.
Tomorrow, we will have a collaboration
with Tokyo Jyushiryu.
Tokyo Advertising Club.
Please come!
Please come.
Please watch!
Did you watch?
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's do our best.
We'll do our best.
Wait a minute.
Julia's grape is going to be crushed.
Grape?
Grape.
Wow!
Please watch the next video too!
That's the information.
Let's crush it!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Attempt no.2
We captured the concept!
Bye!
I want to perform live with my body
full of passion.
I will definitely show you a more
powerful appearance than last year.
I'm really looking forward to the
performance of Senzenburi, who will
support me.
Our mystery story has just begun.
I think everyone can do it.
There is no limit to the possibilities.
If Senzenburi and the members are
together, we can definitely make a big
wall into a small wall.
We believe in that.
So, please look forward to it.
Dash! Dash! Let's chase our dreams!
Dash! Dash! Dash! Never wake up from
this dream!
If I'm with you, I can make my dreams
come true!
I can be your breaking point!